expatengineer.net 2006-08-22

# Privacy

?openagent&bannername=quadrant1 "Employing the right person can add
exceptional value to your business... 
Getting it wrong can be very expensive... 
With so much at risk, we'll help you find
the right person with a minimum of fuss...")?openagent&bannername=Clough120x60EXE "With over 35 projects in 10 countries Clough has many world class and diverse professional engineering opportunities available right now")?openagent&bannername=Petronas120 "Through drive and ingenuity,PETRONAS has in its short history demonstrated remarkable growth and performance to emerge as a Fortune Global 500 company. Incorporated in Malaysia in 1974, PETRONAS has in its 30 years of operations established a global footprint that includes exploration and retail operations in 34 countries, and counts among its 30,000 strong workforce people of 28 nationalities. 
With a robust expansion plan on the cards, PETRONAS invites professionals to embark on a journey of growth and discovery, and chart the path of an emerging global champion. ")?openagent&bannername=Monadelphous120 "Monadelphous are always seeking Project Engineers with mechanical, structural or civil construction backgrounds for construction and maintenance engineering roles. Project Managers and Construction Managers who have managed white- and blue-collar workforces will find Monadelphous has some of the most challenging and rewarding projects in Australia. General engineering and senior project personnel such as Planners, Schedulers, Estimators, Expeditors and Contracts Administrators are also highly sought.")?openagent&bannername=serp120 "Services to Projects, SERPRO, provides consulting services to industrial firms.

Serpro is mainly involved in technical projects. For Oil & Gas Sectors, these projects mainly belong to the development phase. 

Our customers are the contracting authorities or the prime contractors.")?openagent&bannername=Bayside120EXE "Bayside Personnel have extensive opportunities in the Middle East, providing skilled professionals to the petroleum and utility industries for the last 16 years. Bayside Personnel is the sole agent in Australia and New Zealand for Saudi Aramco, the world’s largest oil company.")?openagent&bannername=amec120 "Our ambition is to continue to be one of the world's leading international project management and services companies by bringing added value to our clients, investing in our people and the communities we work with. ")?openagent&bannername=GRDMinproc1 "GRD Minproc is a leading Australian engineering contracting business, providing high value services specialising in the design, engineering and construction of minerals processing and waste-to-resource projects. 
Founded in the 1970s, the Australian public company grew rapidly on the strength of the high quality engineering services it provided to the Australian gold industry. In April 2000, the company was acquired as a wholly owned subsidiary of its major shareholder GRD Limited, a Western Australian engineering and development company. ")?openagent&bannername=Acorp120EXE "AustCorp Recruitment Pty Ltd is dedicated to opening avenues of employment between international companies their projects and engineering and construction personnel from Australia.

")?openagent&bannername=RailPersonnel120x60 "If you're looking for rail industry professionals for your organisation or if you're looking for a job within the rail industry then this site is for you. RailPersonnel is an online search company that matches professional people with some of the rail industry's top positions.")?openagent&bannername=TADPerthEXE120 "TAD is Australia's most successful technical personnel recruitment company. We currently manage over 1,000 contractors and temporary personnel, with a nationally linked database providing access to resources and positions in all parts of Australia and New Zealand and through our International links we are also able to provide the same opportunities in 51 countries world-wide")?openagent&bannername=KCOFC "Feature your company here. Display your 120 x 60 logo with 40 words of text to an International Engineering Audience. Click on the logo for further details")  
|  | 

www.kco.net.au  
www.expatjobs.net  
www.expatengineer.net  
www.jobs-the-engineer.com  
www.engineeringjobs.net.au

This Privacy Policy applies to Kco Pty Ltd, (ABN 88 087 371 248) "KCO" is a private Australian company. KCO is bound by the National Privacy Principles of the Privacy Act, 1988 (Australia) 

KCO, does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. KCO, only collects personally identifiable information from resume postings, the registration process for posting jobs, and mailing list registrations.

KCO, respects your right to privacy. As part of the registration process, we give you the opportunity to decline to receive any mailings from either KCO, or other parties to whom the KCO, may provide such information. Your personally identifiable information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without your approval at the time of collection. 

When you look at our web sites, our Internet Service Provider makes a record of your visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes: 

¨ your server address   
¨ your top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, .uk etc)   
¨ the pages you accessed and documents downloaded   
¨ the previous site you have visited   
¨ The type of browser you are using. 

Information collected may be used internally to create aggregate information about our users. This aggregate data may be provided to our advertisers and sponsors, without providing any personal user data. 

KCO, reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of user behaviour and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. KCO will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties. Also, users should be aware that KCO may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through an KCO, site. 

KCO is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information. 

Users also should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of KCO, 's web servers or through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files a web site can use to recognise repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behaviour and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a user's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Users should be aware that KCO cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties using KCO, to display content. 

If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature. 

Upon request, KCO, will allow any user to "opt out" of further promotional contacts at any time. Additionally upon request, KCO, will use reasonable efforts to allow users to update/correct personal information previously submitted which the user states is erroneous to the extent such activities will not compromise privacy or security interests. Also, upon a user's request, KCO, will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally delete the user and his or her personal information from its database; however, it may be impossible to delete a user's entry without some residual information because of backups and records of deletions. 

The foregoing policies are effective as of Jan 1, 2002. KCO, reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. 

Any questions about this Privacy Statement can be directed to the KCO, Network at privacy@kco.net.au. 

|  |
